{"problems": [
{"question":"49 + 57 = ","id":"0","answer":"106","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"17 + 70 = ","id":"1","answer":"87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"95 + 67 = ","id":"2","answer":"162","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"82 + 72 = ","id":"3","answer":"154","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"60 + 93 = ","id":"4","answer":"153","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"25 + 48 = ","id":"5","answer":"73","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"87 + 52 = ","id":"6","answer":"139","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"25 + 71 = ","id":"7","answer":"96","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"8 + 60 = ","id":"8","answer":"68","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"82 + 84 = ","id":"9","answer":"166","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"48 + 7 = ","id":"10","answer":"55","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"25 + 52 = ","id":"11","answer":"77","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"90 + 95 = ","id":"12","answer":"185","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"29 + 97 = ","id":"13","answer":"126","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"21 + 94 = ","id":"14","answer":"115","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"59 + 2 = ","id":"15","answer":"61","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"91 + 30 = ","id":"16","answer":"121","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"34 + 96 = ","id":"17","answer":"130","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"69 + 69 = ","id":"18","answer":"138","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"94 + 87 = ","id":"19","answer":"181","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"25 + 90 = ","id":"20","answer":"115","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"10 + 70 = ","id":"21","answer":"80","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"86 + 73 = ","id":"22","answer":"159","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"22 + 52 = ","id":"23","answer":"74","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"34 + 18 = ","id":"24","answer":"52","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"28 + 33 = ","id":"25","answer":"61","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"58 + 20 = ","id":"26","answer":"78","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"76 + 11 = ","id":"27","answer":"87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"67 + 82 = ","id":"28","answer":"149","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"19 + 37 = ","id":"29","answer":"56","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"84 + 43 = ","id":"30","answer":"127","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"44 + 43 = ","id":"31","answer":"87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"49 + 39 = ","id":"32","answer":"88","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"86 + 82 = ","id":"33","answer":"168","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"62 + 25 = ","id":"34","answer":"87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"15 + 37 = ","id":"35","answer":"52","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"92 + 67 = ","id":"36","answer":"159","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"71 + 99 = ","id":"37","answer":"170","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"39 + 81 = ","id":"38","answer":"120","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"16 + 86 = ","id":"39","answer":"102","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"81 + 6 = ","id":"40","answer":"87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"46 + 91 = ","id":"41","answer":"137","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"28 + 95 = ","id":"42","answer":"123","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"76 + 37 = ","id":"43","answer":"113","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"8 + 43 = ","id":"44","answer":"51","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"80 + 7 = ","id":"45","answer":"87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"80 + 69 = ","id":"46","answer":"149","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"90 + 23 = ","id":"47","answer":"113","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"19 + 15 = ","id":"48","answer":"34","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"1 + 72 = ","id":"49","answer":"73","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"68 + 91 = ","id":"50","answer":"159","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"41 + 69 = ","id":"51","answer":"110","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"16 + 47 = ","id":"52","answer":"63","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"70 + 7 = ","id":"53","answer":"77","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"59 + 100 = ","id":"54","answer":"159","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"92 + 79 = ","id":"55","answer":"171","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"93 + 79 = ","id":"56","answer":"172","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"19 + 3 = ","id":"57","answer":"22","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"54 + 43 = ","id":"58","answer":"97","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"7 + 31 = ","id":"59","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"19 + 65 = ","id":"60","answer":"84","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"49 + 77 = ","id":"61","answer":"126","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"21 + 44 = ","id":"62","answer":"65","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"19 + 87 = ","id":"63","answer":"106","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"45 + 86 = ","id":"64","answer":"131","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"99 + 91 = ","id":"65","answer":"190","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"51 + 32 = ","id":"66","answer":"83","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"64 + 87 = ","id":"67","answer":"151","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"34 + 36 = ","id":"68","answer":"70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"13 + 69 = ","id":"69","answer":"82","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"69 + 5 = ","id":"70","answer":"74","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"31 + 44 = ","id":"71","answer":"75","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"10 + 66 = ","id":"72","answer":"76","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"24 + 20 = ","id":"73","answer":"44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"12 + 32 = ","id":"74","answer":"44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"43 + 3 = ","id":"75","answer":"46","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"10 + 97 = ","id":"76","answer":"107","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"3 + 82 = ","id":"77","answer":"85","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"61 + 12 = ","id":"78","answer":"73","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"51 + 30 = ","id":"79","answer":"81","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"57 + 44 = ","id":"80","answer":"101","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"69 + 32 = ","id":"81","answer":"101","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"71 + 57 = ","id":"82","answer":"128","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"24 + 61 = ","id":"83","answer":"85","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"18 + 15 = ","id":"84","answer":"33","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"41 + 34 = ","id":"85","answer":"75","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"71 + 46 = ","id":"86","answer":"117","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"58 + 16 = ","id":"87","answer":"74","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"7 + 61 = ","id":"88","answer":"68","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"79 + 13 = ","id":"89","answer":"92","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"95 + 85 = ","id":"90","answer":"180","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"30 + 73 = ","id":"91","answer":"103","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"27 + 10 = ","id":"92","answer":"37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"61 + 82 = ","id":"93","answer":"143","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"70 + 64 = ","id":"94","answer":"134","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"92 + 25 = ","id":"95","answer":"117","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"89 + 5 = ","id":"96","answer":"94","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"72 + 54 = ","id":"97","answer":"126","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"94 + 97 = ","id":"98","answer":"191","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"56 + 99 = ","id":"99","answer":"155","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"},
{"question":"31 - 15 = ","id":"100","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"4 - 29 = ","id":"101","answer":"-25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"53 - 78 = ","id":"102","answer":"-25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"26 - 95 = ","id":"103","answer":"-69","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"47 - 11 = ","id":"104","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"22 - 21 = ","id":"105","answer":"1","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"88 - 100 = ","id":"106","answer":"-12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"91 - 72 = ","id":"107","answer":"19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"69 - 14 = ","id":"108","answer":"55","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"2 - 75 = ","id":"109","answer":"-73","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"78 - 21 = ","id":"110","answer":"57","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"49 - 98 = ","id":"111","answer":"-49","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"83 - 57 = ","id":"112","answer":"26","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"70 - 95 = ","id":"113","answer":"-25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"24 - 59 = ","id":"114","answer":"-35","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"75 - 21 = ","id":"115","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"82 - 21 = ","id":"116","answer":"61","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"10 - 59 = ","id":"117","answer":"-49","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"57 - 69 = ","id":"118","answer":"-12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"9 - 63 = ","id":"119","answer":"-54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"53 - 32 = ","id":"120","answer":"21","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"94 - 27 = ","id":"121","answer":"67","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"66 - 12 = ","id":"122","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"48 - 7 = ","id":"123","answer":"41","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"80 - 41 = ","id":"124","answer":"39","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"54 - 38 = ","id":"125","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"64 - 53 = ","id":"126","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"74 - 49 = ","id":"127","answer":"25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"97 - 7 = ","id":"128","answer":"90","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"25 - 62 = ","id":"129","answer":"-37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"13 - 2 = ","id":"130","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"30 - 42 = ","id":"131","answer":"-12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"34 - 67 = ","id":"132","answer":"-33","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"10 - 62 = ","id":"133","answer":"-52","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"84 - 25 = ","id":"134","answer":"59","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"50 - 23 = ","id":"135","answer":"27","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"24 - 65 = ","id":"136","answer":"-41","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"30 - 71 = ","id":"137","answer":"-41","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"10 - 78 = ","id":"138","answer":"-68","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"91 - 42 = ","id":"139","answer":"49","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"76 - 60 = ","id":"140","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"1 - 88 = ","id":"141","answer":"-87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"84 - 17 = ","id":"142","answer":"67","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"19 - 95 = ","id":"143","answer":"-76","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"29 - 48 = ","id":"144","answer":"-19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"13 - 57 = ","id":"145","answer":"-44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"82 - 28 = ","id":"146","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"65 - 53 = ","id":"147","answer":"12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"38 - 65 = ","id":"148","answer":"-27","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"29 - 46 = ","id":"149","answer":"-17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"33 - 46 = ","id":"150","answer":"-13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"69 - 54 = ","id":"151","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"3 - 75 = ","id":"152","answer":"-72","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"48 - 76 = ","id":"153","answer":"-28","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"43 - 7 = ","id":"154","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"85 - 11 = ","id":"155","answer":"74","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"16 - 68 = ","id":"156","answer":"-52","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"16 - 22 = ","id":"157","answer":"-6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"27 - 27 = ","id":"158","answer":"0","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"66 - 51 = ","id":"159","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"60 - 15 = ","id":"160","answer":"45","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"78 - 2 = ","id":"161","answer":"76","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"12 - 56 = ","id":"162","answer":"-44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"92 - 48 = ","id":"163","answer":"44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"2 - 66 = ","id":"164","answer":"-64","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"49 - 97 = ","id":"165","answer":"-48","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"87 - 46 = ","id":"166","answer":"41","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"72 - 50 = ","id":"167","answer":"22","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"61 - 5 = ","id":"168","answer":"56","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"17 - 44 = ","id":"169","answer":"-27","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"77 - 35 = ","id":"170","answer":"42","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"16 - 67 = ","id":"171","answer":"-51","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"23 - 66 = ","id":"172","answer":"-43","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"36 - 15 = ","id":"173","answer":"21","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"40 - 12 = ","id":"174","answer":"28","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"61 - 83 = ","id":"175","answer":"-22","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"7 - 77 = ","id":"176","answer":"-70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"54 - 3 = ","id":"177","answer":"51","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"17 - 5 = ","id":"178","answer":"12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"15 - 50 = ","id":"179","answer":"-35","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"59 - 98 = ","id":"180","answer":"-39","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"36 - 12 = ","id":"181","answer":"24","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"2 - 92 = ","id":"182","answer":"-90","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"81 - 45 = ","id":"183","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"12 - 49 = ","id":"184","answer":"-37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"62 - 42 = ","id":"185","answer":"20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"41 - 21 = ","id":"186","answer":"20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"55 - 17 = ","id":"187","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"74 - 44 = ","id":"188","answer":"30","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"11 - 1 = ","id":"189","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"39 - 1 = ","id":"190","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"34 - 47 = ","id":"191","answer":"-13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"5 - 78 = ","id":"192","answer":"-73","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"75 - 88 = ","id":"193","answer":"-13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"71 - 81 = ","id":"194","answer":"-10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"65 - 97 = ","id":"195","answer":"-32","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"6 - 37 = ","id":"196","answer":"-31","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"39 - 22 = ","id":"197","answer":"17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"91 - 27 = ","id":"198","answer":"64","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"20 - 23 = ","id":"199","answer":"-3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"},
{"question":"6 * 5 = ","id":"200","answer":"30","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"10 * 5 = ","id":"201","answer":"50","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"4 * 1 = ","id":"202","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"18 * 17 = ","id":"203","answer":"306","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"13 * 2 = ","id":"204","answer":"26","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"6 * 15 = ","id":"205","answer":"90","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"2 * 15 = ","id":"206","answer":"30","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"20 * 11 = ","id":"207","answer":"220","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 18 = ","id":"208","answer":"162","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"13 * 8 = ","id":"209","answer":"104","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"13 * 1 = ","id":"210","answer":"13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"19 * 2 = ","id":"211","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"11 * 7 = ","id":"212","answer":"77","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"6 * 9 = ","id":"213","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"20 * 12 = ","id":"214","answer":"240","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"19 * 16 = ","id":"215","answer":"304","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"13 * 18 = ","id":"216","answer":"234","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"7 * 18 = ","id":"217","answer":"126","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"3 * 20 = ","id":"218","answer":"60","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"3 * 2 = ","id":"219","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"1 * 16 = ","id":"220","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"10 * 8 = ","id":"221","answer":"80","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"11 * 17 = ","id":"222","answer":"187","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"17 * 15 = ","id":"223","answer":"255","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 13 = ","id":"224","answer":"195","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 18 = ","id":"225","answer":"270","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"5 * 7 = ","id":"226","answer":"35","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"5 * 17 = ","id":"227","answer":"85","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 10 = ","id":"228","answer":"150","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"17 * 6 = ","id":"229","answer":"102","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"6 * 7 = ","id":"230","answer":"42","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 12 = ","id":"231","answer":"180","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"3 * 10 = ","id":"232","answer":"30","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"4 * 5 = ","id":"233","answer":"20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"11 * 6 = ","id":"234","answer":"66","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"20 * 7 = ","id":"235","answer":"140","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"11 * 1 = ","id":"236","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"7 * 10 = ","id":"237","answer":"70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"17 * 19 = ","id":"238","answer":"323","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"13 * 20 = ","id":"239","answer":"260","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"1 * 6 = ","id":"240","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"19 * 9 = ","id":"241","answer":"171","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"5 * 12 = ","id":"242","answer":"60","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"10 * 20 = ","id":"243","answer":"200","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"4 * 11 = ","id":"244","answer":"44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"3 * 14 = ","id":"245","answer":"42","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"17 * 3 = ","id":"246","answer":"51","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"6 * 3 = ","id":"247","answer":"18","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"18 * 1 = ","id":"248","answer":"18","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 10 = ","id":"249","answer":"90","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"4 * 13 = ","id":"250","answer":"52","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"1 * 15 = ","id":"251","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"7 * 15 = ","id":"252","answer":"105","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"16 * 2 = ","id":"253","answer":"32","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"1 * 14 = ","id":"254","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"20 * 4 = ","id":"255","answer":"80","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"6 * 20 = ","id":"256","answer":"120","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"12 * 3 = ","id":"257","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"12 * 12 = ","id":"258","answer":"144","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"6 * 4 = ","id":"259","answer":"24","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 11 = ","id":"260","answer":"99","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"7 * 2 = ","id":"261","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"11 * 8 = ","id":"262","answer":"88","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"12 * 10 = ","id":"263","answer":"120","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"10 * 18 = ","id":"264","answer":"180","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"20 * 18 = ","id":"265","answer":"360","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"6 * 13 = ","id":"266","answer":"78","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"4 * 4 = ","id":"267","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"19 * 12 = ","id":"268","answer":"228","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 9 = ","id":"269","answer":"81","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"13 * 17 = ","id":"270","answer":"221","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"11 * 5 = ","id":"271","answer":"55","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"19 * 3 = ","id":"272","answer":"57","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"20 * 20 = ","id":"273","answer":"400","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 4 = ","id":"274","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 14 = ","id":"275","answer":"126","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 5 = ","id":"276","answer":"75","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"19 * 18 = ","id":"277","answer":"342","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"4 * 12 = ","id":"278","answer":"48","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 13 = ","id":"279","answer":"117","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"3 * 16 = ","id":"280","answer":"48","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"5 * 3 = ","id":"281","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"14 * 19 = ","id":"282","answer":"266","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"20 * 14 = ","id":"283","answer":"280","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"4 * 18 = ","id":"284","answer":"72","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"12 * 14 = ","id":"285","answer":"168","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"17 * 1 = ","id":"286","answer":"17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 19 = ","id":"287","answer":"285","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"14 * 15 = ","id":"288","answer":"210","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"10 * 13 = ","id":"289","answer":"130","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"13 * 3 = ","id":"290","answer":"39","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"8 * 14 = ","id":"291","answer":"112","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"5 * 16 = ","id":"292","answer":"80","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 4 = ","id":"293","answer":"60","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"17 * 7 = ","id":"294","answer":"119","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"9 * 8 = ","id":"295","answer":"72","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"14 * 5 = ","id":"296","answer":"70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"14 * 16 = ","id":"297","answer":"224","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"3 * 7 = ","id":"298","answer":"21","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"15 * 15 = ","id":"299","answer":"225","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"},
{"question":"68 / 17 = ","id":"300","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"96 / 16 = ","id":"301","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"52 / 2 = ","id":"302","answer":"26","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"28 / 2 = ","id":"303","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"70 / 35 = ","id":"304","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"64 / 2 = ","id":"305","answer":"32","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"30 / 3 = ","id":"306","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"18 / 6 = ","id":"307","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"28 / 7 = ","id":"308","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"45 / 5 = ","id":"309","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"86 / 2 = ","id":"310","answer":"43","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"15 / 3 = ","id":"311","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"88 / 8 = ","id":"312","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"77 / 11 = ","id":"313","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"50 / 2 = ","id":"314","answer":"25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"50 / 25 = ","id":"315","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"36 / 3 = ","id":"316","answer":"12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"80 / 10 = ","id":"317","answer":"8","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"28 / 4 = ","id":"318","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"80 / 2 = ","id":"319","answer":"40","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"90 / 9 = ","id":"320","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"96 / 48 = ","id":"321","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"76 / 4 = ","id":"322","answer":"19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"66 / 2 = ","id":"323","answer":"33","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"75 / 5 = ","id":"324","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"51 / 17 = ","id":"325","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"98 / 7 = ","id":"326","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"88 / 44 = ","id":"327","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"84 / 21 = ","id":"328","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"22 / 11 = ","id":"329","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"54 / 3 = ","id":"330","answer":"18","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"36 / 6 = ","id":"331","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"26 / 2 = ","id":"332","answer":"13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"22 / 2 = ","id":"333","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"18 / 2 = ","id":"334","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"42 / 21 = ","id":"335","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"80 / 20 = ","id":"336","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"49 / 7 = ","id":"337","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"80 / 8 = ","id":"338","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"42 / 7 = ","id":"339","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"80 / 4 = ","id":"340","answer":"20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"21 / 3 = ","id":"341","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"100 / 4 = ","id":"342","answer":"25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"75 / 3 = ","id":"343","answer":"25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"48 / 4 = ","id":"344","answer":"12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"60 / 12 = ","id":"345","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"98 / 49 = ","id":"346","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"56 / 28 = ","id":"347","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"90 / 18 = ","id":"348","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"66 / 11 = ","id":"349","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"64 / 4 = ","id":"350","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"54 / 27 = ","id":"351","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"63 / 3 = ","id":"352","answer":"21","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"72 / 36 = ","id":"353","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"78 / 3 = ","id":"354","answer":"26","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"60 / 15 = ","id":"355","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"45 / 15 = ","id":"356","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"33 / 3 = ","id":"357","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"57 / 3 = ","id":"358","answer":"19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"84 / 42 = ","id":"359","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"56 / 8 = ","id":"360","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"48 / 24 = ","id":"361","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"48 / 6 = ","id":"362","answer":"8","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"100 / 20 = ","id":"363","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"20 / 10 = ","id":"364","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"76 / 2 = ","id":"365","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"16 / 4 = ","id":"366","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"96 / 4 = ","id":"367","answer":"24","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"65 / 13 = ","id":"368","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"40 / 8 = ","id":"369","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"14 / 7 = ","id":"370","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"92 / 4 = ","id":"371","answer":"23","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"20 / 5 = ","id":"372","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"75 / 25 = ","id":"373","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"82 / 2 = ","id":"374","answer":"41","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"35 / 7 = ","id":"375","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"75 / 15 = ","id":"376","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"78 / 6 = ","id":"377","answer":"13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"68 / 4 = ","id":"378","answer":"17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"48 / 2 = ","id":"379","answer":"24","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"60 / 4 = ","id":"380","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"44 / 22 = ","id":"381","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"45 / 3 = ","id":"382","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"72 / 24 = ","id":"383","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"90 / 6 = ","id":"384","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"60 / 20 = ","id":"385","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"84 / 28 = ","id":"386","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"50 / 5 = ","id":"387","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"32 / 8 = ","id":"388","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"58 / 29 = ","id":"389","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"30 / 15 = ","id":"390","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"36 / 9 = ","id":"391","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"46 / 23 = ","id":"392","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"52 / 4 = ","id":"393","answer":"13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"52 / 13 = ","id":"394","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"60 / 6 = ","id":"395","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"90 / 15 = ","id":"396","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"38 / 19 = ","id":"397","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"8 / 2 = ","id":"398","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"},
{"question":"72 / 3 = ","id":"399","answer":"24","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
]}
